[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Two Moon Junction is the title to a 1988 Robert  Zemeckis film.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "To decant means to pour wine (or other liquid) from one container to another.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The first painting to sell for more than $100,000,00 was painted by this artist.", "correct_answer": "Picasso", "incorrect_answers": ["Degas", "Velasquez", "Van Gough"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 1999 movie The 13th Warrior, Wendol appears as this animal to frighten his enemies.", "correct_answer": "Bear", "incorrect_answers": ["Snake", "Wolf", "Lion"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Actress Susan Buckner portrayed which character from the 1978 movie Grease?", "correct_answer": "Patty", "incorrect_answers": ["Frenchie", "Jan", "Marty"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This marine mammal is known as the pilot whale, but it is not actually a whale. What type of animal is it?", "correct_answer": "Dolphin", "incorrect_answers": ["Walrus", "Seal", "Otter"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which female actress partners with Jet Li in the movie Kiss of the Dragon, directed by Chris Nahon?", "correct_answer": "Bridget Fonda", "incorrect_answers": ["Julie Dreyfus", "Uma Thurman", "Winona Ryder"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What substance does the Brocciu cheese not contain?", "correct_answer": "Lactose", "incorrect_answers": ["Milk", "All of these", "Calcium"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Five Positions, which are the basis of ballet, as well as the starting and ending points for ballet movements, were finally established by Pierre Rameau in what year?", "correct_answer": "1725", "incorrect_answers": ["1800", "1589", "1900"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was supposed to direct Fear and Loathing in Las Vegas, before Terry Gliliam took over?", "correct_answer": "Alex Cox", "incorrect_answers": ["Steven Spielberg", "George Lucas", "David Fincher"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What shocking discovery does detective Mark McPherson make about the murdered Laura in the 1944 mystery movie Laura?", "correct_answer": "She is actually alive.", "incorrect_answers": ["Laura is actually a man.", "Such person never existed.", "She turns out to be his sister."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The movie Waynes World was shot in a little over one month.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]